Guide to the Washington State University Capital Planning Building Files 1957-1998
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Owen Science Library Design Development. 1979. / Harris, Reed and Litzenberger, AIA, Architects; Abam Engineers, Inc., Structural EngineersValentine, Fisher and Tomlinson, Mechanical and Electrical Engineers (Box 15)
- Olympic Weight Room Expansion - Revised. Description of Project; Building Committee; Statement of Problem; Statement of Goals; Planning Criteria; General Considerations; Space Requirements; Specific Requirements. 12/1995. (Box 15)
- Olympic Weight Room Addition - Design Development. 4/1988. / ALSC Architects, P.S.; Campbell Engineers - StructuralRiley Engineering - Mechanical and Electrical Engineers (Box 15)
- Olympic Weight Room Addition - Specifications (construction set). 12/1988. / ALSC Architects, P.S.; Campbell Engineers - StructuralRiley Engineering - Mechanical and Electrical Engineers (Box 15)
- Olympic Weight Room Addition Building Program. 8/1987. (Box 15)
- Olympic Weight Room Facility - Specifications. 6/1985. / ALSC Architects, P.S.; Campbell Engineers - StructuralRiley Engineering - Mechanical and Electrical Engineers (Box 15)
- Olympic Weight Room Facility - Design Development. 3/1985. / Adkison Leigh Sims Cuppage - Architects; Campbell Engineers - StructuralRiley Engineering - Mechanical and Electrical Engineers (Box 15)
- Olympic Weight Room Building Addition - Building Program, Hollingbery Field House. 12/1984. (Box 15)
- P.E Building - Program for the Proposed Gymnasium. 11/1965. (Box 15)
- P.E. Building - Schematic Design Brochure. 11/1966. / Paddock and Hollingbery AIA Architects (Box 15)
- Parking Facility - Design Criteria and Outline Specification. 1500 Car Parking Facility Preliminary Design. 8/1970. / John Graham and Company Architects - Planners - Engineers (Box 15)
- Presidents Residence. Additions and Remodeling to. 1967. / Trogdon-Smith, AIA Architects; Philip E Deene, AIA, Director of Facilities PlanningMechanical and Electrical: Rice. Strecker, and Cook; Structural: Lyerla and Peden; Landscape Architect: L Keith Hells (Box 15)
- Physical Science Building - Schematic Design Brochure. 2/1970. / Naramore Bain Brady and Johanson; Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson - StructuralBouillon, Christofferson and Schairer - Mechanical; Naramore, Bain, Brady and Johanson - Electrical; Paul (Box 15)
- Physical Science Building Phase II - Schematic Design Brochure. 7/1970. / Naramore Bain Brady and Johanson; Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson - StructuralBouillon, Christofferson and Schairer - Mechanical; Naramore, Bain, Brady and Johanson - Electrica (Box 15)
- Physical Science Building Elevator Data. 5/1970. / Prepared By Charles W Larch and Associates (Box 15)
- Physical Science Building - Preliminary Design. 11/1968. / Naramore Bain Brady and Johanson Architects; Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson - StructuralBouillon, Christofferson and Schairer - Mechanical; Naramore, Bain, Brady and Johanson - Electrical (Box 15)
- Publications Building - Schematic Design Brochure. 1967. / Architects: Evanoff and Kabush, AIA; Structural Engineers: Lyerla and PedenMechanical and Electrical: James S. Latenser (Box 15)
- Puyallup - Controlled Environment - Lab and Greenhouse. 1970. / Research and Extension Center; Carlson and James ArchitectAndrew T. Bingham - Structural; Stingle-Atwood and Associates - Mechanical and Electrical (Box 15)
- Puyallup - Office and Lab Facilities. Research and Extension Center. 5/1966. / Naramore Bain Brady and Johanson - Architects; Bouillon, Christofferson and Schairer - Mechanical and ElectricalWorthington Skilling Helle and Jackson - Structural (Box 15)
- Prosser - Rogers Hamilton Laboratory Building. Institute of Agriculture Sciences Irrigation Experiment Station. 9/1961. / Philip E. Deene, AIA; Cowan and Paddock, AIA (Box 15)
- Regents Dining Hall Remodeling - Schematic Design Brochure. 2/1979. / Tan Brookie Kundig Architects; Structural: L. C. CampbellMechanical: Gerard and Associates; Electrical: Wanless - Cook Associates; Good Service Consultants: George E. Bundy and Associate (Box 15)
- Research and Technology Park - Project Manual - Building One. Phase 3 Tenant Improvements. 11/1985. / Taber Chaitin Associates - Architecture, Landscape Architecture, Planning, Interior Design; Charlie Capital Group - Developer (Box 15)
- Research and Technology Park - Project Manual Phase 2 - Site and Weatherskin. 7/1985. / Taber Chaitin Associates - Architecture. Landscape Architecture, Planning, Interior Design; Charlie Capital Group - Developer (Box 15)
- Research and Technology Park - Building One Phase 2. Replaces Addendum No. 1 ENTIRELY. / Taber Chaitin Associates (Box 15)
- Research and Technology Park - Building One Phase 3 - Addendum #6. 2/1986. / Taber Chaitin Associates (Box 15)
- Rogers/Orton Din. Hall - Schematic Design Brochure. / Kenneth W. Brooks, AIA Architects (Box 15)
- Rotunda Dining Hall (RDH) - Renovation Proposal; Packet of Pictures. / John Graham and Company (Box 16)
- Rotunda Dining Hall - Selective Demolition and Asbestos removal. 5/1985. / Walker McGough Goltz Lyerla P.S. - Architect and Engineers; Centrac Associates, Inc. - Asbestos Removal Consultants (Box 16)
- Rotunda D.H. Design Development - Outline Specifications. Construction Cost Estimate. 5/1985. / Walker McGough, Foltz Lyerla, P.S. - Architects and Engineers (Box 16)
- Rotunda D.H - Design Development. 6/1985. / Walker McGough Foltz Lyerla, P.S. - Architects and Structural Engineers; Mechanical and Electrical: Riley EngineeringAsbestos Removal and Lighting Consultants: Centrac Associates; Design Collaborative - Interior Des (Box 16)
- Rotunda D.H - Remodel Engineers Calculations. 9/1985. / Architects and Engineers: Walker McGough Foltz Lyerla P.S.; Mechanical and Electrical: Riley Engineering, Inc.Lighting Engineer. Centrac Associates, Inc. (Box 16)
- Rotunda D.H - Renovation - Building Program. 1/1985. (Box 16)
- Rotunda D.H - Life Cycle Cost Analysis. 4/1985. / Prepared by Riley Engineering, Inc. and Walker McGough Foltz Lyerla (Box 16)
- Rotunda D.H - Project Manual. 9/1985. / Walker, McGough Foltz Lyerla, P.S. (Box 16)
- Rotunda D.H - Project Manual. Selective Demolition and Asbestos Abatement. 5/1985. / Walker McGough Foltz Lyerla, P.S. - Architects and Engineers.; Centrac Associates - Asbestos Abatement ConsultantRiley Engineering - Mechanical/Electrical (Box 16)
- Rotunda D.H. Remodel - Schematic Design Brochure. 4/1985. / Walker McGough Goltz Lyerla. P.S. - Architects and Engineers (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall - Renovation - Project Manual. 10/1985. / Warren Cummings Heylmnan and Partners - Architects (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall Renovation - Life Cycle Cost Analysis. 5/1984. / Warren Cummings Heylman and Partners/Architects Stingle - Atwood and Associates/Engineers (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall Renovation- Design Development. 4/1984. / Warren Cummings Heylman and Partners/Architects (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall Renovation- Hall Residents Proposal. 8/1983. / Warren Cummings Heylman and Partners/Architects 3/ (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall Remodel Building Program. 8/1982. (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall Renovation Design Development. 3/1984. / Warren Cummings Heylman and Partners/Architects (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall Renovation - Schematic Design Submittal. Design Analysis Tabulations; Construction Cost Estimate; Outline Specifications. 12/1982. / Warren Cummings Heylman and Partners/Architects (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall Renovation - Project Manual Draft Copy. 9/1985. / Warren Cummings Heylman and Partners/Architects (Box 16)
- Stimson Hall Landscaping - Project Manual. 2/1987. / Warren Cummings Heylman and Partners/Architects (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodel Phase 2. Volume 2 Sec 15/16. 1/1988. / Architect and Planners: Decker/Fukui Davison; Structural Engineers: Engineers Northwest, Inc.Mechanical Engineers: Halvorson, Beach and Bower. Inc.; Electrical Engineers. Sparling and Associates, Inc (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodel Phase 1 - Project Manual, Volume 1. 6/1983. / Architect and Planners: Decker/Fukui Davison; Structural Engineers: Engineers Northwest, Inc. (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodeling Phase 1 - Project Manual, Volume 2. / Architect and Planners: Decker/Fukui Davison (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodeling - Building Program. 10/1977. (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodeling - Building Program Phase 1. 5/1982. / Architect and Planners: Decker/Fukui Davison (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodeling - Phase 1 Schematic Design Brochure. 11/1982. (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodeling - Building Program Phase 2. 5/1982. (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodeling - Building Program Phase 2. 12/1985. (Box 16)
- Science Hall Remodeling - Schematic Design Phase 2. (Box 16)
- Safety Building - Schematic Design Submittal (Placed alongside of box due to length). / Doudna Williams Phipps Architects (Box 17)
- Student Services Addition - Energy Conservation Report, Life Cycle Cost Analysis. 11/1993. / Riley Engineering, Inc.; Mahlum and Nordfors. McKinley, Gordon (Box 17)
- Student Services Addition - Value Engineering Study Mahlum and Nordfors, McKinley, Gordon. 10/1993. (Box 17)
- Student Services Addition - Scheme E McKinley Gordon. 10/1992. (Box 17)
- Student Services Addition - Schematic Design Submittal McKinley Gordon Architect. 11/1992. (Box 17)
- Student Health Service Remodeling and Addition Schematic Design Brochure. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates - Architects and Planners; Rice and Luhn - Mechanical EngineersWanless-Cook Associates - Electrical Engineers; Peter A. Suden - Structural Engineers (Box 17)
- Students Bookstore - Schematic Design Submittal. / Architect: Trogdon - Smith AIA; Bookstore Planning: Henry Berry Associates, Inc.Structural Engineers Lyerla and Peden; Mechanical Engineers: Rice and Strecker; Electrical Engineers: Joseph M. Doyle and Asso (Box 17)
- Student Bookstore - Addition to. 9/1978. / TSG Architects; Structural: Peter A. SudenMechanical: Rice and Luhn; Electrical: Wanless-Cook (Box 17)
- Student Residential Community (Steptoe). Schematic Design Brochure 200 Apartments. 4/1969. / Architect. Durham Anderson Freed AIA; Landscape Architect: Richard Carothers AssociatesStructural: Harold K. Roe, CE, SE; Mechanical: Benjamin S. Notkin and Assoc (Box 17)
- Student Recreation Center - Project Update. 4/1998. / Architect: Yost Grube Hall Architects (Box 17)
- Student Recreation Center - Schematic Design. 4/1998. / Architect: Yost Grube Hall Architects (Box 17)
- Student Health - Student Health Service Clinic Building Preliminary Brochure (Placed alongside of box due to length). 1963. / Prepared by McClure and Adkison Architect AIA (Box 17)
- Streit - Perham Remodel - Project Manual. 12/1985. / Clayton R. Joyce Architects; Interior Design: Design CollaborativeStructural: H.K. Kim Engineers, Inc.; Mechanical: D. W Thompson Consultant, Ltd.; Electrical Engineers: Louis C. Warner and Co. (Box 17)
- Streit - Perham Remodel - Design Development. 4/1985. / Clayton R. Joyce Architects; Interior Design: Design CollaborativeStructural: H.K. Kim Engineers, Inc.; Mechanical: D. W. Thompson Consultant, Ltd.; Electrical Engineers: Louis C. Warner and Co. (Box 17)
- Streit - Perham Remodel - Specifications - Asbestos Abatement and Demolition. 7/1985. / Clayton and Joyce Architects; Centrac Associates - Asbestos Abatement Consultant (Box 17)
- South Fairway Intramural Field - Schematic Design Report. 2/1992. / Richard Carothers Associates - Landscape Architects. Planners, Civil Engineers, and Surveyors; Subconsultants: Tam, Boyle Heyamoto - ArchitectsRiley Engineers - Mechanical/Electrical (Box 17)
- South Fairway Intramural Field - Construction Document Submittal. 5/1993. / Richard Carothers Associates - Landscape Architects, Planners, Civil Engineers, and Surveyors; Subconsultants: Tan, Boyle Heyamoto - ArchitectsRiley Engineers - Mechanical/Electric (Box 17)
- Swine Center - Design Development Phase II. Livestock Teaching and Research Facilities. 1975. / Architects: ORB Architects Planners Engineers; EISI Engineered Industrial Systems. Inc. (Box 17)
- Swine Center - Design Development Phase II. Livestock Teaching and Research Facilities (Booklet is titled the same as above, contains different supplemental material). 1975. / Architects: ORB Architects Planners Engineers; EISI Engineered Industrial System (Box 17)
- Sloan - Technology Building - Engineering Addition Preliminary Design. 5/1959. / Culler Gale Martell Norrie Architects and Engineers (Box 17)
- Stephenson Residence Center - Preliminary Design Submittal - Third Tower. 1967. / Architects: Walker and McGough, AIA; Mechanical Engineers Lyle Marque and AssociatesElectrical Engineers: Joseph M. Doyle; Landscape Architect Keith L. Hellstrom (Box 17)
- Smith Agricultural Engineering Building - Alterations and Additions. 1966. / Architects: Evanoff and Kabush, AIA; Structural: Lyerla and PedenMechanical and Electrical: James S Latenser (Box 17)
- Spokane Intercollegiate Research and Technology Institute (SIRTI) Design Development. 7/1990. / WMFL, P.S. Architect and Engineers in Association with Arthur Erickson Architects; Structural: WMFL, P.S. Architects, and EngineersElectrical: Riley Engineering; L (Box 17)
- SIRTI Geotechnical Information - Stone Column/Vibro - Replacement Foundation Improvement Work, SIRTI Site, Spokane WA. / Gifford Consultants, Inc. - Geotechnical Consultants (Box 17)
- SIRTI - Project Manual. 4/1991. / WMFL Architects and Engineers; MW Consulting Engineers: MechanicalRiley Engineering: Electrical; SKU: Civil Engineering/ Landscape Architecture (Box 17)
- SIRTI - Building Program. 4/1988. (Box 17)
- Spokane Riverpoint - Health Sciences Building - Schematic Design. / Architect: Integrus Architecture; Structural: Integrus ArchitectureMechanical/Electrical: MW Consulting Engineers; Cost Estimating: Roen Associates (Box 17)
- Spokane Riverpoint - Health Sciences Building - Predesign Study at the Riverpoint Higher Education Park For The Joint Center for Higher Education Integrus Architecture, P.S. 7/1996. (Box 17)
- Spokane Riverpoint - State Archives Facility Eastern Washington Region and Cooperative Academic Library Services (CALS) - Riverpoint Higher Education Park Management. 10/1998. / Prepared for: the Office of the Secretary of State Archives and Records Division (Box 17)
- Spokane - Joint Center for Higher Education. 6/1993. / Trent and Riverside Avenue Properties; Architectural and Structural: Integrus ArchitectureMechanical and Electrical: MW Consulting Engineers; Property Management: R.W. Robideaux and Company (Box 17)
- Spokane University District Development - Preplanning and Schematic Design. 9/1988. / W.M.F.L., P.S. Associate Architects: Arthur Erickson Architects (Box 17)
- Todd Hall Addition - Building Program DCVRs To be Kept With as Built Drawings. 1963. / C. D. Contractors, Inc. (Box 18)
- Todd Hall Addition - Specifications Volume I of II. 4/1989. / The Henry Klein Partnership; Mechanical: Notkin Engineer, Inc.Electrical: Sparling and Associates; Structural: ABKJ; Landscape Consultant: Jongejan/Gerrard/McNeal Kitchen Consultant: Forma; C (Box 18)
- Todd Hall Addition - Specification Volume II of II, Mechanical and Electrical With Addendums Attached. 4/1989. / The Henry Klein Partnership; Mechanical: Notkin Engineer, Inc.Electrical: Sparling and Associates; Structural: ABKJ; Landscape Consultant. Jong (Box 18)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Specifications (three binders). 12/1993. / The Henry Klein Partnership, Architects (Box 18)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Building Program. 6/1992. / Architect: Cardwell/Thomas and Associates/Architects (Box 18)
- Thompson Hall - Feasibility Study, Foley Institute for Public Policy and Public Service. 1/1995. / Architect. Cardwell/Thomas and Associates/Architects (Box 18)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Schematic Design. 6/1994. / Architect: Cardwell/Thomas and Associates/Architects; Structural: Ratti, Swenson, PerbixMechanical: Path Engineers, Inc.; Electrical: Elcon Associates, Inc.; Cost Control: Ackroyd. Inc. (Box 18)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Design Development Supplemental Information. Estimate of Construction Cost; Program Area Comparison; Architectural Details; Structural Notes; Mechanical Narrative; Light Fixture Schedule. 11/1994. / Ackroyd, Inc. Cardwell/Thomas and Associates (Box 18)
- Thompson Hall Remodel Project. Results of Subsurface Explorations and Floor Slab Moisture Survey. 6/1995. / Gifford Consultants, Inc. - Geotechnical Engineers (Box 18)
- Thompson Hall Remodeling - Former Administration Building Remodeling De Neff Deeble and Barton Architects. 1975. / Rice, Strecker and Cook Professional Engineers (Box 18)
- Supplemental Appendix to the Energy Conservation Report and Life Cycle Cost Analysis. 12/1992. / Mechanical: Path Engineers. Inc.; Electrical Engineer: Elcon Associates, Inc.Architect: Cardwell/ Thomas and Associates (Box 18)
- Todd Hall Addition - Schematic Design Brochure. 1963. / Architect: John W. Maloney, AIA; University Architect: Philip E. Keene, AIA (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Addition - Building Program Statement. 12/1983. (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Addition - Site Selection Study. 2/1984. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Addition to - Schematic Design. 11/1987. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Renovation - Remodeling Program. 5/1990. / The Henry Klein Partnership; Structural: KPFFMechanical: Nolkin Engineering; Electrical: Sparling and Associates (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Preplanning Documents - Outline Specifications, Cost Estimate and Drawings. 7/1990. / The Henry Klein Partnership, Architects (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Schematic Design. 4/1992. / Architects: The Henry Klein Partnership,; Structural: Andersen Bjornstad, Kane, JacobsHalvorson, Beach and Bower Sparling and Associates, Inc.; Acoustical: Michael R. Yantis Associates (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Design Development Submittal. 7/1992. / Henry Klein Partnership, Architects (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Schematic Design Submittal. 7/1992. / Andersen Bjornstad Kane Jacobs, Inc. (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Renovation Feasibility Study. 5/1992. / Morrison Knudsen Corporation (Box 19)
- Todd Hall Renovation - Health and Safety Plan, Demolition of Lead Paint Containing Material. 3/1994. / RZA AGRA, Inc. - Earth and Environmental Group (Box 19)
- Troy Hall Remodeling - Schematic Design Brochure. 1971. / Duglas C. Durkoop, Architect; Rice and Luhn, Mechanical EngineersJoseph M. Doyle and Associates, Electrical Engineers (Box 19)
- Tri-Cities University Center - Building Addition. 2/1988. (Box 19)
- Tri-Cities University Center - Master Planning Report. 6/1988. / Architect: The McKinley Architects, PSC; Associate Architect: Dillman - Luvaas Architects, P.S.Civil and Structural Engineers: KPFF: Consulting; Civil Engineering Consultant to KPFF: Lin and A (Box 19)
- Tri-Cities University Center - Schematic Design. / Architect: The McKinley Architects, PSC; Associate Architect: Dillman - Luvaas Architects, P.S.Civil and Structural Engineers: KPFF Consulting Engineers; Civil Engineering Consultant to KPFF: Lin and Associ (Box 19)
- Tri-Cities University Center Addition Addendum No. 1. 2/1990. / The McKinley Architects PSC (Box 19)
- Tri-Cities Campus - Consolidated Information Center (C.I.C.). 12/1993. / Integrus Architecture, P.S. (Box 19)
- Tri-Cities C.I.C. - Schematic Design. 10/1994. / Integrus Architecture, P.S. (Box 19)
- Tri-Cities Campus - Science and Education Center - Predesign Report. 6/1998. / SRG Partnership, PC (Box 19)
- Tri-Cities C.I.C - Predesign Study. 5/1994. / Prime Architect and Structural Engineers Integrus Architecture P.S.; Mechanical and Communications Electronics Consultants: MW Consulting EngineersElectrical Consultants: Elcon Associates, Inc.; Cost Estimating (Box 19)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Project Manual - 99% Construction Documents Submittal, Division 1 - 14. 6/1995. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates; Structural: Senson Say FagetMechanical: Path Engineers; Electrical: Elcon Associates; Estimate: Ackroyd and Associates (Box 20)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Project Manual - 99% Construction Documents Submittal, Division 15 - 16. 6/1995. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates; Structural: Senson Say FagetMechanical: Path Engineers; Electrical: Elcon Associates; Estimate: Ackroyd and Associate (Box 20)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Bid Package No. 2. Specification for Appendix A - Hazardous Materials Abatement Project. 3/1998. / Prepared by Ed Delorme, OHST AHERA Project Designer # 940511-05 while employed by: SCM Consultants. Inc. (Box 20)
- Thompson Hall Renovation - Abatement Specifications and Contract Documents. 6/1995. / Prepared by: Edward S. DeLorme, OHST AHERA Project Designer #940511-05 while employed by: SCM Consultants, Inc. (Box 20)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Division 15 Mechanical. 4/1998. (Box 20)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Bid Package II - Project Manual. Volume I Divisions 0-8 Project No. 94-1-024. (Box 20)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Bid Package I: Demolition - Project Manual. 6/1997. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates/Architects (Box 20)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Bid Package II Project Manual. Volume I Divisions 1-7 Project No. 94-1-024. 3/1998. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates (Box 20)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Bid Package II Project Manual. Volume II Divisions 8-16. 3/1998. / Cardwell Thomas and Associates (Box 20)
- Valley Road Multi - Use Recreation Fields - Phase 2 Developments. 3/1998. / RCA/Huitt - Zollars, Inc., Prime Consultants; Tan-Heyamoto, ArchitectRiley Engineering, Mechanical-Electrical Engineers; Gifford Consultants, Geotechnical (Box 21)
- Van Doren Hall - Facility Condition Survey. 7/1990. / SCM Consultants, Inc. Architects and Engineers (Box 21)
- Visitor Center Site Study - Comprehensive Physical Planning Process. 11/1988. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture (Box 21)
- New Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Design Development. 3/1990. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates - Architects and Planners (Box 21)
- New Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Schematic Design. 3/1990. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates - Architects and Planners (Box 21)
- Veterinary Research - Diagnostic Center - Schematic Design Material, Western WA Research and Extension Center. 12/1988. / Gtde Weisenbach; Foil Wyatt Mckewen (Box 21)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital Interim Report. 2/1988. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates - Architects and Planners (Box 21)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - A Report on Site Planning. 11/1988. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture, Campus Planners (Box 21)
- Veterinary Science Building - Design Development, Multipurpose Animal Holding Facility. 9/1981. / Naramore Bain Brady and Johanson (Box 21)
- Veterinary Science Building - Site Evaluation and Recommendation, Multipurpose Animal Holding Facility. 9/1980. / The NBBJ Group (Box 21)
- Veterinary Animal Holding Facilities - Schematic Design Brochure. 6/1978. / Barnard and Holloway, Architects (Box 21)
- Veterinary Science Building (Bustad) - Design Development. 1/1975. / Architects: Maloney, Herrington. Freesz and Lund; Structural: Skilling, Helle, Christiansen and RobertsonMechanical and Electrical: Valentine, Fisher and Tomlinson (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Engineering/Life Science Building - Schematic Design. 6/1998. / Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Grasca Partnership; Electrical: PAE Consulting Engineers, IncLandscape Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership; Civil Engineer: Kato and Warren, Inc. (Box 21)
- Vancouver Campus Circulation - Preliminary Design. 6/1998. / Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership Electrical: PAE Consulting ,Inc.; Landscape: Zimmer Gunsul FrascaCivil: Kato and Warren, Inc.; Soils Engineer. Geotechnical Resources; Planning and En (Box 21)